seoservicescanada.ca 2011-12-26

# Privacy Policy

SEO Services Canada is committed to protecting your privacy. This policy outlines our personal information handling practices for both online and offline data. If you give us personal information, we will treat it according to this policy.

When SEO Services Canada collects any personal information via a corporate or sponsored website, we will express our need for the personal data at the point of collection. Personal information is any information that can be used to identify an individual, and may include, but is not limited to, name, email address, postal or other physical address, title, occupation, and other information required to provide a service, deliver a product, or carry out a transaction you have requested. We will only use your personal information in the way we specified when it was collected. We will not subsequently change the way your personal information is used without your consent.

**Unsubscribing**

If you receive an email from us, each email includes instructions on how you can unsubscribe from that particular mailing.  
**  
Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell or rent your personal information to third-parties for marketing purposes unless you have granted us permission to do so.

We may respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process by disclosing your personal information and other related information, if necessary. We also may choose to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

We may collect and possibly share personal information and any other additional information available to us in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of SEO Services Canada’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

We will ask you for your opt-in consent to share your personal information with a third party for any other reason.

**Security of your personal information**

SEO Services Canada is committed to protecting the personal information you share with us. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit.

We recommend you to take every precaution in protecting your personal information when you are on the Internet. For example, change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers when creating passwords, and make sure you use a secure browser.  
**  
Data retention**

SEO Services Canada will not retain your personal information longer than is necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected or as required by applicable laws or regulations.

Please contact us for more information about our privacy policy.
